This is the General Form of a
quintic polynomial equation in one variable, x.
We could solve it easily if we
didn't have all these intermediate x powers.
To make a start, we might first try to get
rid of the quartic, or x to the fourth, term.
In other words, transform it into so-called reduced form,
where the coefficient of this term is zero.
This operation is technically known as a Tschirnhaus Transformation,
the simplest example of which is a linear substitution,
such as x = z + some constant h.
Let's use this to express all these x powers in terms of z.
Expand these powers.
Multiply out the binomials.
Distribute the original coefficients.
Now recall that this first z equation is
just the sum of the six below it.
All seven of these equations are identities, true
for every choice of x and corresponding z.
If we now consider the case z equals one, then
all of these z powers disappear from the matrix.
Now we can read the matrix column by column, to get
expressions for the new coefficients in terms of the original ones.
This H substitution avoids a lot of ugly fractions
with powers of five denominators in the results.
Finally we have succeeded in eliminating the quartic term.